




const data = [{
    id : 1,
    question : "React is a ____",
    op1 : "Javascript library",
    op2 : "Javascript framework",
    op3 : "Both of the above",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "Javascript library"
  },{
    id : 2,
    question : "ReactJS uses _____ to increase performance",
    op1 : "Virtual DOM",
    op2 : "Original DOM",
    op3 : "Both of the above",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "Virtual DOM"
  },{
    id : 3,
    question : "In ReactJS, props can be used to pass",
    op1 : "Properties to the component",
    op2 : "Event handler to component",
    op3 : "Both of the above",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "Both of the above"
  },{
    id : 4,
    question : "The state in react can be updated by call to setState method. These calls are",
    op1 : "Synchronous in nature",
    op2 : "Asynchronous in nature",
    op3 : "Are asynchronous but can be made synchronous when required",
    op4 : "None of above",
    answer : "Asynchronous in nature"
  },{
    id : 5,
    question : "As soon as the state of react component is changed, component will",
    op1 : "Does nothing , you have to call render method to render the component again",
    op2 : "re-renders the component",
    op3 : "be created again from scratch",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "re-renders the component"
  },{
    id : 6,
    question : "React Lifecycle method static getDerivedSateFromProps(props , state) is called when",
    op1 : "Component is created for the first time",
    op2 : "State of the component is updated",
    op3 : "Both of the above",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "Both of the above"
  },{
    id : 7,
    question : "componentDidMount lifecycle method is called when____",
    op1 : "Component is created for the first time",
    op2 : "Component is updated",
    op3 : "Both of the above",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "Component is created for the first time"
  },{
    id : 8,
    question : "Everything in react is __________",
    op1 : "module",
    op2 : "component",
    op3 : "package",
    op4 : "class",
    answer : "component"
  },{
    id : 9,
    question : "React Js is developed by",
    op1 : "Google",
    op2 : "Microsoft",
    op3 : "Facebook",
    op4 : "None of the above",
    answer : "Facebook"
  },{
    id : 10,
    question : "What is the default port for webpack dev server?",
    op1 : "3000",
    op2 : "8080",
    op3 : "3306",
    op4 : "8809",
    answer : "8080"
  }

]


export default data